Made in ABC
So, what are you going to do?
I'll pay you an extra $20,000 after this.
What are you going to do?
This $10,000 is the money you gave me for the tea.
And the extra $20,000 after that is...
the money you gave me as an adult.
What are you going to do?
What if...
What if what?
I become a high school student?
I told you before.
My policy.
That's the best.
Isn't that crazy?
It's not crazy.
Because I...
I just don't know who you are.
I just want to be with you.
I know I was in need of money.
Rena.
This.
You can take it.
Thank you.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go.
It was fun today.
Thank you.
See you on Tuesday.
You know.
You call me a doormat.
People often make mistakes.
But they forgive themselves and live on.
I've been all alone today.
I've been all alone until I laugh.
Feel so bad
Don't run away.
You can always change your mind, baby.
Feel so bad
Take the step out.
What's the meaning of the word right now?
What are you doing?
Are you doing it again?
That kind of love is a lie
It's so bad, don't run away
It'll change anytime, baby baby
The
home psychology is, as I explained earlier,
one that is used to say that there is a very small possibility of achievement in a situation
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
When the light hits you,
you can see how it looks.
Hey, hey, hey!
One more lap!
Look ahead!
Good morning!
Really?
Let me take your picture.
Please.
Yes.
I'll take it.
This is Seiyo Gakuen.
Yes.
A video?
Look, Mizu, I saw it.
I saw it too.
TikTok is really buzzing.
Did you hear that?
Psycho Kachi is good.
That's amazing.
You're a celebrity all of a sudden.
It's not that important.
What is it?
Is this okay?
It looks good, doesn't it?
What?
What is it?
Let me see.
Wow, it looks really good.
This is the real thing, isn't it?
I'll try it.
Let's go.
This is quite a big deal, isn't it?
This is the third generation.
This is Mizu and Amo.
Why are they doing this?
It's a young Italian.
It hurts so much that it hurts already.
It doesn't have to be expanded, does it?
There's a meaning to the expansion.
What does it mean?
In other words, it's a desire to prove oneself.
I don't want to do anything.
I just want to stand out.
I can understand a little.
But the voice lately is too terrible.
But people who do bad things have a sense of coolness.
They have a sense of coolness.
They are strong and dangerous.
They are good for girls in school.
It's not like that now.
It was popular in the past.
That's the third generation.
That's right.
It's the example of the exiles.
I understand if you say that you admire the poor.
But it doesn't mean that it's a trouble video.
No, no.
I think that the people who laugh a lot and are called by everyone are getting popularity.
This is a personal opinion.
The guy who has a good look, has a good athleticism, is a good student, and is not a good fighter.
I want to get a sense of it from everyone.
I want to be popular with girls.
Aren't you going to the tendency?
I do.
You sure do.
I'm a young man, you know.
You're a great man.
Yeah.
I've had a lot of jobs in the past few years.
But when I was younger,
there were a lot of idiots.
There were.
Alcohol and cigarettes were much more loose than they are now.
Loose?
There are a lot of vending machines.
You can buy alcohol and cigarettes.
Really?
I bought alcohol and cigarettes at a convenience store.
Yeah.
What's that?
There were people smoking on the train.
What? On the train?
I don't get it.
In the old days,
there were vehicles that smoked on the train.
What?
A smoking space?
No, just seats.
That's hell.
Also,
you can wear it.
What do you mean?
It's for people with disabilities.
What?
You can ride it for free.
There were a lot of people who bragged about that.
That's a great era.
Did high school students drink alcohol?
Yeah, they did.
After the school festival,
the teachers knew we were going to drink together,
so they told us not to make a fuss.
Really?
If you drink, you'll be an idiot.
That's true.
During my college days,
one or two people would be drunk at the end.
What?
After drinking,
people would smoke on the train and run around.
What kind of trend is that?
That's the trend now.
It doesn't make sense from 1 to 10.
I think it was special.
It's too special.
Even now, young people are idiots.
Japanese men.
If it was back then,
everyone would be recording
and bragging about it.
It's either social media or not.
I think so.
Adults who watch videos and make a fuss
aren't in a position to say anything to young people.
Do we need to give young people a chance to grow up?
Even so,
schools don't have to be responsible for their students.
No.
That's not the case.
I'll tell you.
Yes.
This time,
our students have caused you a lot of trouble.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell the students.
Is this really what we teachers should do?
They tell us to laugh our asses off.
Even though it's for the sake of the students,
it's tough.
Talking to them...
Bad things are bad things.
You'll be punished.
You understand, right?
I didn't think this would happen.
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry for them.
If you're going to cry, don't do this.
I can't contact the two of them.
Miss!
What happened to Horamizu and Kotomi?
Are you going to go to college?
I'm not allowed to go home.
So you're going to go to college.
I guess so.
This time, the company I work for is going to watch me a lot.
So it wasn't a big deal.
But there's been a little bit of a stir on the internet.
I think Mizu-kun and Amo-san will still suffer.
So it's going to be something I can't get back.
Everyone, be really careful with how you use social media and TikTok.
But this is something I can teach at school.
You don't have to do that in the first place.
There's a theory.
But there's a lot going on in the test period.
Komura, who was full of himself, has a lot of sense of satisfaction.
But really, everyone, protect the rules as a high school student and as a person.
Protect yourself.
You're always in a bad mood.
You think it's not a big deal.
But there's a lot going on in your life.
It's the same with alcohol and smoking.
Teacher, can I talk about my point of view?
Go ahead, Sugiyama-kun.
You can talk.
Thank you.
You're not listening.
In the first place, it's not good for the body of a child.
It's not good for the body of an adult.
So it's right to ban alcohol and smoking at home.
It's started.
Someone stop it.
The American tobacco company has been lying for a long time that it has no harm to the body as a result of an investigation.
History has proven that.
It is not supposed to be believed that it is a tobacco.
The government should propose a law.
I'm asking you to be a politician.
I'd like to hear more, but that's it for today.
That's all.
It's over.
Rei.
Goodbye.
Sugaya-san.
Yes.
I think I talked about it before.
I want to talk to my mother this week.
Can you give me the location at 2 o'clock?
I understand.
Over there.
Kougen.
Kougen, what are you doing here?
I don't know.
What?
You know.
Are you still getting along with your ex-girlfriend?
It's not about drinking water.
Life will be over in one shot.
It has nothing to do with you.
Don't say that.
You said it was you.
It's annoying.
Annoying or disgusting.
You smoked.
What?
You must have smoked.
You said it was you.
I said it was you.
Kougen.
You again.
Don't you study hard?
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you mean?
I mean, the new school.
Right?
It's up to you.
That's because you're smart.
You're so lame.
You don't have the guts to give up from the beginning.
What?
You're so lame.
I don't smoke.
You're so lame, Kougen.
You're so lame.
Kougen.
Okido.
Are you going to take the college entrance exam?
No, I'm not.
You're late.
Kougen, you're late.
Why didn't you come?
I'm sorry.
I can't believe I'm so late.
I'm surprised that the teacher always comes home early.
I thought so.
Good morning, Inada.
Good morning.
You're Miyasaka, right?
Yes.
You play the guitar, right?
Yes, I do.
Do you want to play a band with me?
A band?
I'm in a hurry.
It might be more difficult than this.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You don't look well.
Are you sick?
It's your fault.
Half of it.
I've been like this for a long time.
Miyasaka, are you serious about playing a band?
You were in the exam group, right?
It's not the time to play, is it?
I'm going to make you stand out.
Miyasaka, can I talk to you?
I don't need it.
Yamamoto said he quit the band.
That's right.
By the way, that's not a limit, is it?
Yamamoto, can I talk to you?
Yes.
I have a question.
What is it?
Well...
Do you want to play a band?
I don't want to.
I just quit the band and I have an exam.
I don't want to play a band because it feels like a temporary festival.
Miyasaka, can you play a band with me?
Did you start something?
No, I'm going to be a vocalist.
Miyasaka, are you good at singing?
Thank you.
Yamamoto was real.
Because he's my boyfriend.
Let's do it. Please.
I can't do it because my parents will kill me.
I'll study.
How do you do it?
Please.
You're early today.
Yes.
That's enough.
I'm a little late today.
I'm sorry about that.
If you're stressed, tell me.
I'm going out with Koton.
What?
You're going out with Koton?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I haven't been there recently.
Alligator.
Is that it?
That's it, right?
I'm getting weird.
Then I'll go with this.
What was that on that day?
Thank you for waiting.
Let's go.
This is it.
I see.
Excuse me.
Please.
Please hurry up.
I'm sorry to bother you.
My name is Sasaoka.
You're so young.
You're so cute.
Are you really single?
Thank you.
I'm surprised.
Don't you work at home?
What are you talking about?
Your salary is low.
You're handsome.
I'm Yamazoe of Fukutani.
Fukutani?
You're so cool.
I'll play with you next time.
I'll give you service.
Thank you.
Lena,
I'm so excited to have a teacher like you.
Excuse me.
Don't you want to drink?
You can't drink?
I can drink, but not today.
That's fine.
Of course you don't need a substitute.
Let's have fun.
They're not here to drink.
I know.
They're here to talk.
I have a business to talk about.
While drinking.
This is normal when we talk.
My life.
Stop it.
I don't know.
What was it?
Did you do something wrong again?
I don't know.
She was in trouble when she was in middle school.
She's smart.
She's like me.
You got into high school.
Your grades are good, right?
My grades are good.
You're late.
That's a little...
It can't be helped.
Mom!
Stop drinking.
Why are you so cranky?
She's always cranky.
She's scary.
Men don't like cranky women.
She always says that.
Here's your snack.
It's about the path I took today.
Lena, did you get a job or a new school?
I don't have a choice but to get a job.
Are you thinking about getting a new school?
That's normal for your grades.
You can go to university.
You can go to university like Tokyo University or Keio University.
You're well-known for going to university.
But if I work hard...
Wait a minute.
Lena, what do you want to be in the future?
Have you decided what you want to be?
I haven't decided yet.
If you haven't decided, why did you go to university?
I haven't decided yet, so I'll go to university and think about it.
If you want to do something during that time, you should play.
That's not true.
It's not that age.
It's not a school society.
Companies that are doing well now have nothing to do with school.
It's not good to go to a company that cares about school.
After all, it's not a water business.
It's not the best.
The president who came to visit me the other day said that my company had nothing to do with school.
The president of Ikeike who appears on TV came to visit me.
Sasaoka.
Yes.
Not a teacher.
I understand.
It's a waste of time and money to go to university.
But it's a waste of time and money to go to Ikeike.
Do you know?
Do you know that there are a lot of people who have a lot of money in school?
My friends Kato and Hara don't have a lot of money in school.
Who are you talking about?
But the important thing is Lena's feelings.
Feelings?
Lena wants to study all her life.
I don't want to work. I want to study all my life.
Should I do that?
No, it's not like that.
Life is a place to earn money.
Money.
It's money.
It's a place to earn money.
If you go to university because you want to study, you won't study.
It's very expensive.
Even if you graduate and get a job, you can't go to a big company.
Is that so?
The person who earns money is a person who earns money regardless of his or her academic background.
The person who earns the most in Japan and gets the National Education Award is not a person who wants to study.
It's a person who's into baseball.
So it's up to you how you make your life.
That's why I don't think it's meaningful to go to college.
I think it makes sense.
Does it?
The teacher says it's over, but in reality it's not.
What do you think?
As an educational system, we don't teach how to live in this country.
It's true that it's said to be a way of loading.
In any school, the grade is important.
Even if the students go to a good place to study and get a good grade,
it's not a question of whether they're having a good life.
But you can get into a better company.
It's a question of whether it's a good life to go to a good company.
There are many things that make a good company good.
Thank you for the vegetable sticks.
Thank you.
What's the point of working?
Some people say that it's ideal not to work because of early retirement and fire.
I think everyone admires that way of life.
I don't think it's a life just for playing.
No matter what kind of life you live, it's about whether you feel happy or not.
I think the pursuit of happiness should be done in education.
The pursuit of happiness is well-being.
We're happy as humans, and we're living an ideal life.
We're living a life that people can be proud of.
No matter what others think of us, we're living a life that we're satisfied with.
Don't you think teachers should be happy to convey that?
I'm proud of myself.
It's the first time in two or three months.
That's right.
But I'm not sure if I'm happy.
I'm not sure if I'm being shown.
Teachers should think about that a lot.
That's right.
It's not about money, it's about love.
Don't you think people who are serious about that might be living the best life?
I think so.
Mr. Goh, you'll be shivering if you're like that.
Really?
Don't you think you're fooling around with girls like that?
No, no, no.
I'm sure you are.
You've never fooled Haru-chan, have you?
That's because I'm the one who's fooling around.
I'm always fooling around.
What's wrong?
I did it. I did it so well.
Are you done with your homework?
Don't work too hard. Lena is watching you today.
You've been so serious for three years.
Maybe that's right.
Did something happen?
I saw something I didn't want to see.
What? What do you mean?
You know what?
You have to be responsible for what you do.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't be so stubborn.
Do it.
No.
Hurry up and do it.
Ms. Sawaiya.
How was it?
Did you get to talk to your mom?
That's how it is.
I don't think her way of thinking is going to change.
I think you should go to college.
I think what your mom says makes sense.
But you only have one life.
If you have any regrets, I don't think you should give up so easily.
You have to live a life that you're satisfied with.
Even so, it's a realistic problem.
Like money?
I see.
There is a scholarship system.
If you really want to go to college, I think you can do it.
I'll look into it.
It's not that much.
It's not that much to go to college.
You don't have to spend time for me.
You don't have to push yourself.
But Ms. Sawaiya...
I don't want to bother you.
I'll take care of myself.
It's not a bother.
Hey, how are you?
Hi.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Yes?
Good morning.
What's going on?
Ms. Iro!
The police just called!
The police?
Is it okay to go inside?
Or should I park in a coin park nearby?
By the way, what's the parking fee in this case?
It's free.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
I thought you were going to call me.
But you insisted on contacting the teacher.
I told you many times.
We know who his father is.
You know him, right?
Yes.
If your father finds out, he'll kill you.
What about Kouken?
The local gangsters had a fight with the gangsters in other areas.
I'm sorry.
He's a car driver.
He's not involved in the fight.
He's not allowed to drive.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I stopped him for a night because I couldn't find him.
Other gangsters found him.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you don't talk to him, you're banned from the school.
OK.
Let's talk about other things.
Kouken, let's talk.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll take him home, ok?
OK.
I'll talk to your father.
Do you talk to your father often?
Almost.
I see.
Why?
I don't know.
My father is busy and I don't talk to him.
Do you know why he quit Yakuza?
Do you know?
Yakuza is bad these days.
It's not because he doesn't like it.
Did your father say that?
I don't know.
He used to say it was good, but now it's not.
I see.
Do you have a reason?
Do you know why I don't know?
It's like this for a man and a woman.
What?
Did you play with your father often?
Yes.
I see.
What do you mean?
My father wanted me to go to college.
You don't want to say that.
It doesn't matter if you go to college.
You're right.
There are people who think that going to college is no good.
I'm sorry.
I understand that.
But I don't want you to go to college.
What do you mean?
I want you to be happy.
I want you to be happy by going to college.
I want you to go to college because I feel the possibility.
I'm sure of it.
If you want to go to college, I'll go with you.
Do you want to do your best?
I can't do that.
I'm a beginner now.
I have to level up to go to college.
Let's do our best.
What are you doing?
Why don't you leave me alone?
I don't want to get involved with you.
I told my father that I wanted to quit yakuza.
It's a promise.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't want you to walk the same path as me.
I don't want you to become a yakuza.
I don't want you to do that.
I can't be a yakuza without a message.
Your father was crying.
He was crying while making ramen with me and Mr. Ryo.
He was so powerful.
You know, your father...
You're the one who loves me the most,
but you don't have to be like that.
Right?
Let's go to school.
I'll bring you some food.
But don't tell everyone that I brought you food.
I will.
Say hello to Mr. Ryo and Mr. Kyoto.
Okay.
And if you want to study, come to my house.
Hello.
Ryo.
You're late.
How long have you been sleeping?
I'm not sleeping.
Mr. Okido, I have a suggestion for today.
What is it?
Would you like to lend me the notes for this morning's class?
Sugiyama.
I'll lend it to you.
Thank you.
Are you going to quit?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay.
You're pretty late.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I brought Kougen here.
Oh, I heard.
Kougen wants to get out of here.
Mr. Ryo.
He did it.
He's a pro.
Aika, you're drinking too much.
Hit him.
Right.
I'm sorry, it's hot.
You look like you're having a good time.
Dad...
Do I look like this when I wash my feet?
You idiot.
That's a hundred times better.
Here you go.
Thanks for the food.
I've had a lot of trouble since April.
You took me here last time.
I see.
It ended in the evening.
You really care about me, don't you?
I see.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
It hurts, but...
It's so good.
I'm sorry.
For all the trouble.
Dad.
Thank you.
I can't get over my own weakness
But, you know,
Everyone is full of worries
I'm still alive today while searching
I'll send you a song
Stopping my tears for just one moment
I will sing this song for you, my friend
Sing this song with love
Sing this song with sympathy and empathy
Just by not noticing
Love is overflowing
In everything around you